iscripts.com 2009-02-14

# iScripts.com, paid and free opensource PHP web scripts and software. Create turnkey web business in social networking, virtual mall, online swapping, image hosting, site builder using our web apps

---|---|---|---  
  
We recognize the importance of protecting the privacy of personal information about our customers. Personal information includes all of the personally identifying information that is provided to us. We are sensitive to these privacy interests and believes that protecting valuable personal/financial information is one of our most significant responsibilities. 

The policies outlined below describe our policies to protect your privacy. 

**:: Use, Collection and Retention of Client Information**  
We collect, retain and use only the information about our customers that is required by law to administer our business and provide high level services to our clients. We retain this information no longer than necessary to meet these objectives. All transmitted credit card information is handled securely through digitally encrypted Secure Socket Layers (SSL) technology. 

**:: Spam Policy**  
Spam is flooding the Internet with many copies of the same message, in an attempt to force the m/*essage on people who would not otherwise choose to receive it. Email spam targets individual users with direct mail messages and costs the sender very little to send. Most of the costs are paid for by the recipient or the carriers rather than by the sender. 

We don't condone the use of spam and the sending of unsolicited email in any form, nor do we control other web sites involvement and/or practices in this area.

**:: What information do we collect?**  
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.  
Like most websites, we use cookies and/or web beacons to enhance your experience, gather general visitor information, and track visits to our website. Please refer to the 'do we use cookies?' section below for information about cookies and how we use them. 

**:: What do we use your information for?**  
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs).

  * To process transactions  
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested by the customer. 
  * To send periodic emails  
The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

**::How do we protect your information?**  
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information.   
We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.  
After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be kept on file for more than 60 days.

**:: Do we use cookies?**  
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.   
We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

**:: Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect others or ours rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**::Third party links**  
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**::California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**  
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.  
As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the 'Edit Profile' page.

**::Children's Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**  
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children's Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**::Online Privacy Policy Only**  
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**::Terms and Conditions**  
Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at iScripts.com.

**::Your Consent**  
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

**::Changes to our Privacy Policy**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

**::Contacting Us**  
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.   
www.iScripts.com  
84 Whitman Dr  
Schaumburg, IL 60173  
support@iscripts.com  
(312)423-6728

| 

|   
---  

|  |  |    
---|---|---  
  
[FAQ](http://www.iscripts.com/faq.php) |  [News Letter](http://www.iscripts.com/newsletter.php) |  [Forum](http://www.iscripts.com/forum/index.php) |  [Terms](http://www.iscripts.com/terms.php) |  Privacy  |  [Disclaimer](http://www.iscripts.com/disclaimer.php) |  [Legal Notice](http://www.iscripts.com/legalnotice.php) |  [Site Map](http://www.iscripts.com/sitemap.php)  
---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---
